Police are releasing tear gas bullets to control the new video of Jahangir Puri violence.
Another video of Jahangir Puri violence shocked.
Some local people are collecting sticks.
These are pictures taken against taking the sticks in the CCTV.
In Delhi, the Minister of Ministry of Defence has filed a NSA on the five main accusations of Jahangir Puri.
The 26th accused in the Jahangir Puri riots, Ghulam Rasool alias Gulli, who gave weapons to Sonu Sheikh, was arrested by the police.
The court sent four-day police custody against the main accused of Delhi violence.
The Delhi violence investigation is in full speed.
The investigation is being conducted from the angle of the PFI of the Crime Branch.
It is not right to reveal the details of the investigation.
The Crime Branch is investigating it and the District Police is fully supporting it.
On the third day after the violence, the police were very alert.
The BJP supporters have posted pictures of the main accused of Delhi violence.
On the decision of the U.P government, the Congress raised the question.
The U.P government raised the question.