Funtime Kids
The best use of time
The person who makes the best use of time
gets good results with time
This is what happened when Sonu and Vani's
annual exams were about to come
Hey, are you still studying?
Come, let's eat
Only a small project is left
If we don't do it, the teacher will scold us
And the exams are starting from next week
Vani was a very hardworking
and a good use of time kid
Whereas her brother Sonu
was a very careless and naughty kid
He used to postpone everything
Is your project done?
Yes, the project has to be done
in the 6th period
There are still 2 periods left
I will do it quickly
Now come fast, I am hungry
And I have to play too
Hey Sonu, wait
If you don't do it, the teacher will scold you
Sonu and Vani's parents
always used to give Sonu
an example of Vani and make him understand
Look Sonu, you have grown up now
Along with playing, you should
also concentrate on your studies
Yes mummy, from tomorrow for sure
Sonu, learn to make good use of time
from your sister
Look, she studies with time
She plays with time
She never postpones today's work
for tomorrow
You see, from tomorrow
I will also do the same
Shall I go and play now?
Please!
Sonu's carelessness was increasing
day by day
And finally
the days of the exams
were nearing
Only 2 days were left
for Sonu and Vani's exams
Listen, from next Monday
your exams are starting
right?
Study hard
and do well in the exams
Sonu, I am
really worried about you
You always postpone
today's work for tomorrow
Don't postpone your studies for tomorrow
Like Vani,
study all the lessons on time
Okay?
Papa, there are still 2 days
left for the exams
I will study everything
I am going to play now
Till I don't play
I won't be able to study
Vani, look
what a beautiful weather
Come, let's play
for a while
We can study later
Everything will be done soon
Yes, the weather is beautiful
But I have to
complete my lessons
Tomorrow is the exams
Playing in this weather
is something else
You keep studying
I am going to play
After a while, Vani saw
that the beautiful weather
is slowly taking the form of a storm
And the dark clouds
are swirling
This can happen anytime
Seeing the weather
Vani was worried
that if it rains
how will she complete her lessons
Because in the rains
the electricity of the house
is cut off
She called out to Sonu
Sonu, listen
It looks like it's going to rain
Maybe the electricity will be cut off at night
Stop playing and
come and complete your lessons
What will you write to me?
Don't worry, Vani
It's afternoon now
I will finish everything
at night
The electricity won't be cut off
It will be fun to study
after the rain
I am going now
Sonu played till late evening
But she was worried
when the rain started
Sonu got scared
and returned home
She saw that
there was no electricity
in the entire village
Seeing this
Sonu started crying
What will happen to me
in the exam tomorrow?
I didn't study a single lesson
And now there is no electricity
I will fail
I told you
to study your lessons
on time
I told you a week ago
to study on time
But you never understood
Now suffer
Sorry, Papa
What do I do now?
I wish
I had studied my lessons
on time
She understood
that because of her carelessness
she didn't have time to study
Crying won't help
Now do you understand
why everyone used to explain you?
Now stop crying
and come with me
I had completed my studies
on time
I will teach you all the lessons
and remind you
The next day
both the children went to the exam
The one who respects time
in the future
is great!