Police is releasing tear gas bullets to capture the new video of Jahangir Puri violence.
Another video of Jahangir Puri violence shocked.
They are collecting sticks.
Some locals had done it.
There are pictures of protest against taking the sticks in CCTV.
In Delhi, the big case of Jahangir Puri riots was put on NSA on 5 main accused.
In Jahangir Puri riots, 26th accused Sonu Sheikh was arrested.
Ghulam Rasool alias Gulli was arrested by police.
Delhi violence chief accused Park Kasa was arrested by police for 4 days.
Full speed Delhi violence investigation is going on.
Evidence is being collected from crime branch team.
Investigation is also going on from the angle of PFI.
It is not right to reveal the details of the investigation.
Crime branch is investigating it.
District police is fully supporting it.
After violence, 3rd day of Jahangir Puri violence, police forcefully arrested.
BJP supporter posted pictures of accused Ansar on social media.
This cap is sticking on him.
By wearing cap of Bharatiya Jagata Party.
According to mastermind of Jahangir Puri riots.
BJP surrounded Kejriwal government for Delhi violence.
It is said that riots are happening because of setting up Bangladeshi and Rohingya.
Rewards are given to such people.
Delhi chief minister has settled in Okhla and Jahangir Puri.
BJP was surrounded for Delhi violence.
It is said that riots are happening because of Nagarnigam elections.
BJP supporter Giriraj Singh said that Ram Navmi Jalush is happening in Pakistan.
It is said that Ram Navmi Jalush is happening in Pakistan.